pure-jobs.com 2017-01-01

# Privacy policy - Please read the pure-jobs.com privacy policy

**1\. Profile and Your information:**  
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and explains data collection and use practices for Purejobs. The Purejobs includes all Web pages, newsletters, discussion forums and lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by Purejobs and each of its wholly-owned subsidiaries. By accessing Purejobs site/network, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**2\. Do you collect IP addresses?**  
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the Purejobs, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our Sites. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the Purejobs, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our Web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors.

**3\. What are cookies?**  
From time to time, Purejobs or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of Purejobs you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers and we may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our Site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

**4\. How do you use single-pixel gifs?**  
Purejobs and its advertisers may use single-pixel gif images, sometimes referred to as web bugs or web beacons, to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information. Purejobs does not gather personal information through the use of these images. Our advertisers may use single-pixel gifs that can track personal information from cookies that may have been previously placed on a user's computer by an advertiser.

**5\. What personal information do you collect?**  
Wherever Purejobs collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, e-mail address, phone number, work or home address, information about your job function, information about Purejobs, and credit card information.

We may request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a contest or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to announcement lists or information about conferences and trade shows). Participation in contests or other promotions on the Purejobs Network is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose personal information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes.

If you are purchasing something on the Purejobs, we, and any third party provider, need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date. This allows us, or third party providers, to process and fulfil your order and to notify you of your order status. Credit card and e-mail information will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose except as provided in this Privacy Policy without your express permission.

Purejobs also offers access to some services that require registration. We may use your registration contact information to send notification to you of products and services by e-mail and/or postal mail. We may share that information with our clients and they may also send you promotional materials. We may also use your IP address internally and share it with third parties.

When you sign up for a Purejobs e-mail newsletter, you are given the opportunity to sign up for targeted third-party mailings. Whether or not you want to receive these announcements is your choice. If you choose to receive an announcement from a specific distribution list, you will receive commercial messages from independent third parties that have contracted with Purejobs to send messages to the list. You may stop the arrival of these announcement lists at any time by removing your e-mail address from the list by forwarding the announcement list to [](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy110%20=%20'privacy'%20+%20'@';%20addy110%20=%20addy110%20+%20'pure-jobs'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy110%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy110\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E) [ ](mailto:privacy@purejobs.com) [ ](mailto:privacy@purejobs.com)[](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy4679%20=%20'privacy'%20+%20'@';%20addy4679%20=%20addy4679%20+%20'purejobs'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy4679%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy4679\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E) [privacy@purejobs.com](mailto:privacy@purejobs.com) or by following the instructions on the e-mails you receive.When you use co-branded services, or those provided by a third party, within the Purejobs, your information may be passed to the co-brand or third party provider and their use of your information is subject to their applicable privacy policies.

**6\. Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**  
Purejobs will disclose personal information and/or an IP address:

\- To contact you regarding other products and services which may be of interest to you (including those we may offer jointly with other companies). At any time, however, you may opt out of such contact;

\- When required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

\- Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Purejobs;

\- Protect and defend the rights or property of the Purejobs of sites and related properties, or visitors to the Purejobs of sites and related properties;

\- Identify persons who may be violating the law, the Purejobs legal notice and Web site User Agreement, the rights of third parties, or otherwise misusing the Purejobs or its related properties;

\- Fulfil a user's order or request;

\- To process and fulfil your order or notify you of order status;

\- When we have your consent to share the information;

When you use co-branded services within our network of sites, you grant us permission to pass your registration information back to that service partner. Their use of your information is subject to their applicable privacy policies.

We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent or as permitted by this Privacy Policy.

**7\. What else should I know about my privacy when online?**  
The Purejobs contains many hyperlinks to third party Web sites. The Purejobs also contains advertisements of third parties. Purejobs is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party Web sites or advertisers. Purejobs does not share any of the individual personal information you provide Purejobs with the third parties to which Purejobs links, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although Purejobs may share general, aggregate data with such third parties (such as how many people use our Site). Please check with those Web sites to determine their privacy policy.

If you Purejobs's discussion threads, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these discussion threads. In order to avoid your e-mail address or other personal information from being gathered and used by others for inappropriate or harmful purposes, Purejobs advises that you should be cautious about posting a real e-mail address or other personal information to newsgroups, chats, or other public forums.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Certain Purejobs media properties use a shopping cart feature that safeguards this information by using industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted servers. SSL codes the information transferred between you and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information. Other Purejobs media properties do not use SSL and thereby do not offer a secure coded way to transfer information.  

**8\. Business transfers**  
We are always seeking to improve our network of Web sites and our business. In accomplishing these objectives, we may sell a company, assets or websites or one or more of the companies in our corporate family may merge with, or be acquired by, another company. In connection with the foregoing, we may transfer some or all of your information in order that the service being provided to you may continue or for other business purposes.

**9\. Your Consent To This Agreement**  
By using the Purejobs Network, you consent to the collection and use of information by Purejobs as specified above. We reserve the right to modify this Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Please note that your use of the Purejobs Web sites is governed by our Legal Notice.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  [ ](mailto:admin@pure-jobs.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy)[](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy91062%20=%20'admin'%20+%20'@';%20addy91062%20=%20addy91062%20+%20'pure-jobs'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy91062%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy91062\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E) [admin@pure-jobs.com](mailto:admin@pure-jobs.com)[.](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy21786%20=%20'jaylartey'%20+%20'@';%20addy21786%20=%20addy21786%20+%20'ymail'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy21786%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy21786\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E.) At www.pure-jobs.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.pure-jobs.com and how it is used.  **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.pure-jobs.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.pure-jobs.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.pure-jobs.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.pure-jobs.com and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - [ ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)[](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google AdsenseThese third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.pure-jobs.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.pure-jobs.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.pure-jobs.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
